<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on going on an adventure!</title>
    <link>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on going on an adventure!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 14:16:32 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On My Way to Kevin Bacon</title>
      <link>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/on-my-way-to-kevin-bacon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 14:16:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/on-my-way-to-kevin-bacon/</guid>
      <description>Traveling is funny sometimes. In a lot of ways, it gives me a huge appreciation for just how big and diverse the world is. It can be awesome to marvel in the size of it all. On the opposite vein, the more I travel, the more I realize just how small and connected the world is. Connected through the internet, yes, but what I really mean is connected through networks of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Specifically Pacific</title>
      <link>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/specificallypacific/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:42:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/specificallypacific/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was my last day in Taiwan before classes begin. The way I saw it, it could have been a day of rest, preparing for the weeks of class ahead, or a day of activity, taking advantage of one last day with no homework or looming classes.
The beach was three buses and a train away, about 90 minutes of transit. None of the other people Berk and I have met yet wanted to get up early or spend so long on public transit, so we headed out by ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language Goals</title>
      <link>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/languagegoals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 16:01:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/languagegoals/</guid>
      <description>Despite being less than a week in, I’ve recently had the realization that I’ll never achieve perfection in this language. The absolute best I think I might possibly achieve is functionality, mediocrity, even proficiency—but not without a heavy accent and frequent mistakes. White-guyness notwithstanding, nobody is ever going to mistake me for a native Mandarin speaker.
I’m beginning to understand that the amount of time and effort required to reach a near-native level is… insane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 22-24</title>
      <link>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/june22-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 23:12:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/june22-24/</guid>
      <description>An action packed past few days have made it feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve been here a lot longer than I have. In a good way.
Thursday: spent the day touring and doing various activities with Gerry (水壓機). Snapped some photos, pet some geese, and borrowed some beer mugs from dadaocheng wharf.
Friday:On this day, my body began to realize I played a nasty joke on it by flipping my clock backwards. Still, I give Taipei Museum of Fine Arts 9/10 stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good morning from Taipei</title>
      <link>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/firstday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 05:54:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/firstday/</guid>
      <description>5:30am.
It&amp;rsquo;s funny how different the trees are here. The leaves are thick and waxy and if they were everywhere you&amp;rsquo;d be in the jungle. You don&amp;rsquo;t think about the trees being different.
Berk and I got a taxi from the airport last night and made it to the apartment around 8pm, which (amen and hallelujah) does exist. Gerry, the roommate I corresponded with online also exists, but I&amp;rsquo;m less sure he is real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pirate&#39;s log 1: en-route</title>
      <link>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/en-route-to-taipei/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://elliotdurkee.com/posts/en-route-to-taipei/</guid>
      <description>Berk is getting me another coffee. It&amp;rsquo;s 3am Taipei time (12:04pm SF time) and trying to beat the jet-lag in advance is going poorly. First leg of the journey is complete: 4 and a half hours from CLE to SFO felt slow. Not ecstatic for the next 14 hours to TPE. Berk rates bidets highly and the polaris lounge is for posers and pundits, but not pirates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
